[Fated Hearts]
[Episode 19]
Mister,
do you know
who's the owner of this carriage?
Who are you?
This carriage
belongs to Miss Ruyan.
We just brought her back not long ago.
Which young master sent you here?
Please go and tell him
Miss Ruyan has just left
and that she won't be back
until tomorrow.
[Ruyan]
Here you are.
Thank you, Sister Xueying.
It turns out that looking from this spot,
one can see everything
on the street clearly.
Was Wu Ying's appearance that day
not a random event?
Two bowls of noodles.
She seemed to be waiting for someone
that day.
Was it that maid from the dance house?
Sister,
where did you go just now?
What happened?
Nothing.
Are the kids
all full?
They made a competition out of the eating.
After you left,
I bought them one more bowl of noodles.
They ate that much?
Kids, when we're back,
you'll practice the horse stance.
No sleep until you hold the stance
for two hours.
Master,
is it too late to spew up
-the noodles now?
-Master...
Master, I'll spew them out too.
Me as well.
It's too late.
How can you sleep when you're stuffed?
Master...
Stop whining, or I'll make it four hours.
Xueying,
are you familiar with Yujing City?
I'm looking for a smithy.
There seems to be one
next to the pharmacy.
[Wutong Mansion]
Come out.
Come on.
Slowly.
Miss Yixiao.
You're back.
What happened to you?
Seems like someone lashed out at you.
Did the First Prince get mad
because
Sister and I went out for a stroll?
I'm fine, all safe and sound.
Is he back?
His Highness is waiting for you inside.
-Brother!
Brother!
Brother,
can I go to your armory again
for a visit?
Yes, sure.
Pick whatever you like.
Take them to the armory.
Keep them safe from the sharp weapons.
Yes.
Thank you, Brother.
Off you go.
Let's go.
I'll give you a tour!
There are many weapons in the armory!
Let's go!
What's this about?
I'm a third wheel now, aren't I?
You could've just said it out.
I'd know my cue to leave.
Nine,
let's go.
Anything wrong?
What exactly happened?
His Majesty got sick,
and is now in a coma.
But don't you worry.
Lord Ling
is attending to His Majesty in the palace.
I'm actually worried about you.
His Majesty suddenly fell ill.
One can safely assume
that things in Yujing City
will soon become unpredictable.
As the First Prince,
you're about to be
dragged into danger.
Under any circumstances,
keeping yourself safe
is the top priority.
Got it?
Oh, right.
I want to tell you something.
So do I.
You go first.
Are you going to blame me
for going out without guards?
It's true that my hand is injured,
but I don't have disabilities.
Please don't make a fuss over it.
What were you trying to tell me just now?
Take Fang and the kids away.
♪ The rain drifts endlessly ♪
Go back to Zhengnian Villa
♪ The old dream burns the heart ♪
with Young Mistress Ling.
My father is seriously ill.
♪ Dreams sink into ruin ♪
Prime Minister Zhuang
will take over the court soon.
♪ Missing the warmth of your palm ♪
By then,
he'll wield immense power
with control of all the six ministries.
I'm worried that they might go after you,
♪ Awaiting dusk ♪
because they're aware...
♪ Shadows take root in the mountain pass ♪
that you're my biggest weakness.
♪ In just a moment, tears stained ♪
Nothing in my life can be my weakness,
♪ Amid the bustling sound
of wind and rain ♪
except for Xiyang
♪ Who laughs at me,
heart cold as the desert? ♪
and you.
♪ Dreams turn through a lifetime ♪
I already failed to protect Xiyang.
There is no way I'll let you...
♪ Who sighs for me,
enduring separations? ♪
Okay.
I'll do as you said.
♪ Love is a trial, harsh and cold ♪
You've agreed to that?
♪ Who crushes the lingering pain for me? ♪
Does it look like I'm joking?
♪ Clouds vanish, rain ceases, seek me ♪
Yixiao,
I didn't mean to be so blunt about it.
On my way back,
I was thinking
how to put it diplomatically.
But being pressed for time,
I had to react fast.
I understand.
It's good to be straightforward.
I was planning to leave anyway.
Now, this is perfect.
What were you going to tell me earlier?
It doesn't matter now.
Don't worry.
Just focus on what you need to do.
Master!
Shunzi, Fang,
go get Sister Xueying.
We need to pack up our stuff quickly.
We're leaving right away.
Why so surprised?
Go start packing now.
You're leaving right away?
The clock is ticking.
I would hate to be a burden
or a liability to you.
Go.
Be quick.
Master...
What are you waiting for?
No more dawdling.
Fang, keep up!
Yes!
Yixiao.
Yixiao!
Fang told me you would leave soon.
That's right.
Not only I,
but also Nine, Fang, Shunzi, and you
will be leaving.
I have to leave too?
Yes.
[Wutong Mansion]
Come with me.
What happened?
Just come!
Your Highness,
Miss Yixiao
is leaving with those kids.
Their carriage is at the door now.
We can still catch up with them.
The city gate will be closed soon.
We have to set out now,
or they'll be gone!
Hands off!
Yun Fang,
Send two guards
to escort them.
Tell the guys to lay low.
Yujing City is facing
many uncertainties now.
They won't be safe until they're away.
Yes.
I hope Miss Yixiao will understand
what Your Highness's efforts are for
someday.
[Wutong Mansion]
It wasn't until they camped at night
did I notice
Miss Yixiao was nowhere to be seen.
She must have secretly
gotten off the carriage halfway.
Your Highness,
it seems Miss Yixiao and her fellows
didn't leave the city at all.
What about Miss Ling and the children?
I've already sent people
to continue protecting them,
to make sure
they arrive at Zhengnian Villa safely.
Why don't I have some people
go look for Miss Yixiao?
No need.
Do you know where she was off to?
How am I supposed to know?
Are we not going to look for her?
If anyone asks about her,
just tell them this—
Fu Yixiao has gone
with Young Mistress Ling
to Zhengnian Villa.
-Yes.
Sir.
Sir,
no one else
has seen this mask, right?
You specifically asked me
to keep it secret.
Rest assured.
I know the rules.
[Lotus Pavilion]
Sir, please come in.
Sir, to the second floor.
Come this way.
Sir, careful.
[Lotus Pavilion]
Come visit us again!
Mr. Wang!
Gentlemen, come on in.
Miss Ruyan!
Hello, Miss Ruyan.
These gentlemen
have been waiting here since yesterday.
Too bad that they haven't realized
not everyone
gets to see you dance.
Oh, right.
A lady just came to the dance house,
asking to meet with you.
A lady?
However,
I don't know
where she is now.
Miss, you do
recognize this mask.
W-What an unconventional mask.
Is it yours?
After the Battle of Pingling,
someone took your carriage
to the Jinxiu military camp.
Do you remember that?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
You don't?
That day, you had that girl
go to the back alley to deliver a note.
She also read what was written on it.
"Stand by outside Yujing City."
Why would the death camp
follow your orders?
Miss, you must be mistaken.
What "death camp"?
I'm just a dancer.
Still in denial, huh?
That girl already confessed.
Tell me
everything you know.
Or I won't be nice to you.
I've told you I know nothing!
You just won't tell, right?
Then there's no choice
but to talk somewhere else.
As I said,
I know nothing.
Abducting me won't help.
Kill me, if you have the guts.
You want to die?
I'll grant your wish.
Not there.
Aim for this spot.
Slit it with all your strength.
The pain will disappear within an instant.
You'll only feel extremely cold
all over your body.
Then you'll get drowsy.
Very sleepy, I'd say.
Ending a life...
is actually easier
than it sounds.
What now?
Can't bring yourself to do it?
Then don't pretend
not to fear death.
After all, nothing can be
more important than staying alive.
Don't you agree?
I've told you
I know nothing.
I did have a note delivered,
but I really didn't know
the content.
Also, I don't understand
a single word of what you just said.
Did he ask you to deliver the note?
I'm curious.
What's your relationship with him?
All you need to know is
that I'll never betray him.
I'd rather die
than sell him out.
Such admirable loyalty.
You're so devoted to him.
Are you in love with him?
Look at you,
completely lovestruck.
You defend him all the time.
I guess I'm right.
I won't tell you who he is.
Don't waste your time
fishing for information.
The news of you being abducted
will soon
spread throughout Yujing City.
Venture a guess.
Will that man you fancy
come to your rescue?
You don't seem to be sure
whether he truly cares about you or not.
How about this?
let's make a bet,
on whether he'll come or not.
He... He won't come here.
He's well aware
that I'll never betray him.
I bet he will come,
though not in person.
Instead, he'll send someone
to kill you.
That's impossible.
He won't do that.
Whether you betray him or not,
he'll silence you permanently—
he even doesn't need to do it himself
—because only your death
can guarantee there won't be witnesses,
and that his plans won't be sabotaged.
It can't be true.
He won't have me killed.
You don't believe it?
Then wait and see.
Actually, I deliberately left clues.
I purposefully used your carriage
to bring you here.
Following the carriage tracks,
he'll find this place.
If he doesn't send anyone to kill you,
then I'll set you free.
And I promise to never give you
a difficult time again.
But if things turn out as I said,
you must tell me everything
you know.
Shall we bet on it?
My Lord, you're His Eminence's ally.
May I ask
if His Eminence has safely escaped?
I think he has ordered you all
to do my bidding from now on.
I have one rule here—
you are only to execute my orders,
and not to ask any questions.
Yes.
My Lord, previously, you asked us
to stand by outside Yujing City.
All the members of the death camp are here
at your service now.
You will find it worthwhile
to risk your lives for me.
When my great mission is accomplished,
you'll all have a share of the glory.
Now, your task
is to kill a person for me.
Your Highness.
Here's a message from Grandmaster Ling:
His Majesty has not yet come to.
Neither has his condition worsened.
Grandmaster Ling
wished you not to worry too much.
I got it.
Concerned about your health,
he made a prescription for you
in particular.
Please have Your Highness's physician
prepare the herbs.
Thanks.
[Licorice roots: 5 grams; Steamed rehmannia roots: 50 grams;
White atractylodes and Chinese angelicad: 25 grams each]
Your Highness.
There was a disturbance
at the dance house.
A dancer named Ruyan
was taken away.
Ruyan?
This must be related to her.
To whom?
Tomorrow, the authorities
will surely search for Ruyan.
Keep an eye on how it develops.
Create some trouble for them in secret.
Just do as I say.
Got it.
Miss, do you like any one of them?
This one.
Miss Ruyan
was abducted by a young woman.
You guys, search
each household down the street!
Bring all the women you find suspicious
back to the office!
-Yes!
Miss, wait!
What are you doing?
Officer Lu,
we're ordered by the prefect
to investigate
the abduction of Miss Ruyan.
You're from the Capital Prefecture Office?
Yes.
The Capital Prefecture Office
is responsible for maintaining order
in the capital.
So instead of fulfilling
your duties assigned by His Majesty,
you chose to
waste your time on such trivial matters?
Here is the First Prince's command!
All of you shall guard
outside the imperial palace.
Do not ask a single question
about those trivial matters.
Do you hear me?
-Yes!
Let's go!
Your Highness,
I've found
the soldier who poisoned
the war horses in our camp.
However...
He must be dead now.
In the woods near our military camp,
we discovered his body.
In his tent,
hidden silver taels were found.
He was probably bribed
and then killed.
If my deduction is correct,
this must be
Prime Minister Zhuang's doing.
I'll go on with the investigation.
If we can get something
on him through this case...
No need.
Prime Minister Zhuang is a weasel.
He already killed that soldier.
There is no way he'd leave a trail behind.
Your Highness...
Your Highness,
Shen Wu the Minister of Rites
is requesting an audience.
[Wutong Mansion]
Your Highness,
I was planning
to go to Princess Xiyang's villa
to check and cart the dowry
prepared by Your Highness
before transporting it to Jinxiu.
Since
Your Highness's supervision is needed
in this matter,
I had to come and trouble Your Highness.
Get my horse ready.
I'm leaving for the villa.
[Wutong Mansion]
Yes.
So,
Your Highness is going to
monitor the process
in person?
That's wonderful!
Ahead lies Shengjing City.
Everyone, take a rest here!
Yes!
Lift up your head.
Your father passed away
before
he could leave a will.
Should I make you the emperor
or let Jingyan take the throne?
Mother,
I'm devoid of the competence
to assume the throne.
But many court officials
think highly of you.
This has truly put me
in a difficult position.
Since you've admitted to
not being qualified for the throne,
I should kindly grant your wish
of guarding Zhennan Pass
in Pingling City.
Off you go then.
My Prince,
when was the last time you came back
to Shengjing City?
A long time ago.
Then I guess this trip
will bring back many memories for you.
Here's good news for you.
Father praised you again today,
saying that you're gifted, bright,
and exceptionally smart,
and that I lag far behind you.
You're just a worthless wretch
given birth by a lowly maid.
Who are you to be compared with me?
[Jingming Garden]
Let me conduct one more check.
Guys,
make sure you count every item right.
Be extra careful!
Yes.
[Jingming Garden]
Your Highness,
here is the list of Princess Xiyang's
dowry
for your review.
[List of Dowry]
I watched Princess Xiyang
grow up.
Seeing Her Highness leaving Susha,
I felt like
there was a void in my heart.
As the verse goes,
"the royal abode stands silent
in the wind;
nobody responds to the rain
in the bamboo groove;
[Jingming Garden]
the gone princess is not to be
heard or seen;
though a thousand miles apart,
we watch the same moon over the roof."
Xiyang is all by herself.
She must feel lonely.
Go make arrangements.
Send Xiyang's maids and servants
to Jinxiu along with the dowry.
Your Highness,
if there's nothing wrong about the list,
I'll load the dowry into the carts.
Go ahead.
[Jingming Garden]
Check one more time.
Cart the items if everything's alright.
Get a move on.
Your Highness,
here's a message from Song Cheng.
Trails of those people
were found outside the city.
There's an ambush. Run!
You recognize those women, don't you?
You've seen for yourself.
I was right, wasn't I?
Spill the beans now.
I did lose the bet.
But I still won't tell you
who I'm working for.
At this point,
you're still protecting him?
He attempted to kill you.
Yet you still choose to cover for him?
I'm just a dancer.
How could you take the word
of a member of the debased caste?
Nobody would ever miss
someone like me,
even if I died.
Kill me now.
I knew you'd break your word.
But it doesn't matter.
I can still
find out who he is without your help.
Here I am, Miss.
Go, puppy.
They went that way.
Are you sure?
Is it confirmed?
Rest assured.
The scent lingers within the nearby 10 li.
Go!
[Susha Kingdom's Feng Battalion,
Song Cheng]
Your Highness.
What did you find?
I finally found traces of them
after spending 7 days and nights
studying and tracking trails.
This way, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
There's a jumble of footprints here.
At least dozens of people
gathered here last night.
Your Highness, look here.
But...
what can these footprints
possibly tell us?
Song Cheng
is a top-class tracker.
He used to be a constable
at the Court of Judicial Review.
Then His Highness recruited him
into the army.
He had a nickname back then—
the Clairvoyant Constable.
With just his keen eyes,
he can distinguish foes from friends
by analyzing footprints on a battlefield
where a thousand people have stood.
Your Highness,
this way.
The footprints extend to this very spot
and split up here.
If my judgment is correct,
those people separated here
in order to
set an ambush.
Your Highness,
we'd better stop here
to avoid alerting them.
Yun Fang,
if I'm not mistaken, anyone who is to
reach Yujing
from the Capital Garrison
must take this road.
That's right.
Xia Jingshi has indeed fled from Yujing,
but his death camp still stays put.
These people
are all skilled assassins.
Their mission must be
about assassinating someone.
Hou Jing the Minister of War
left for
the Capital Garrison a few days ago
for an inspection.
When will he return to Yujing?
The estimated time of arrival...
is tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow morning...
They're targeting Minister Hou!
We're running out of time.
This is the place.
[Murong Residence]
Murong Residence?
You failed?
Fu Yixiao set up a trap.
She's still in Yujing City?
That explains it.
She must've tracked down Ruyan.
Why don't we
find a way to eliminate Fu Yixiao?
You two are no match for her.
Did she find you out?
We took several detours
and made sure no one
was following
before we came back to Your Lordship.
You were found out.
We're ready to be punished
for failing the task, Your Lordship.
The cat is out of the bag.
There's no point punishing you.
Does Your Lordship have a plan then?
[Wutong Mansion]
Miss Yixiao?
Shouldn't you be
at Zhengnian Villa now?
You came back without telling Suige?
I get it.
You must've missed him too much.
In recent days,
His Majesty's serious condition.
has been upsetting him.
I'm glad you're back.
I hope you can comfort him.
It seems
Ruyan has told you everything.
Aren't you tired?
How am I not?
Then drop the act.
I happen to
have a question for you today.
Feng Suige considers you
his best friend.
Why do you have to hurt him?
What?
You don't want to talk here?
Then let's go inside
and talk in front of Feng Suige.
Is it what you want,
to turn me and him against each other?
Am I turning you two
into enemies,
or are you feeling bad
about betraying him?
Why are you colluding
with Xia Jingshi?
Don't worry.
Nothing I do
will cause harm to Feng Suige.
In the Battle of Pingling,
if I hadn't shot Feng Suige
and knocked him off his horse,
he would've entered Zhennan Pass
and died there.
Do you expect me to believe what you said,
that you wouldn't harm him?
If I truly wanted to kill him,
I could have it done in many ways.
He never guards against me.
Answer me.
What exactly do you want?
Be patient.
You'll see soon enough.
Aren't you afraid I'll tell
Feng Suige the whole truth?
Of course I am.
Why else would I be waiting here?
You can tell him
what I'm really like anytime.
But you should know
that I'm not alone.
I'm only part of a team.
If my cover is blown,
my plan will be executed
ahead of schedule.
[Wutong Mansion]
Let me put it this way.
The moment you step
into Feng Suige's residence,
someone in the imperial palace
will jeopardize His Majesty's life.
Just imagine.
What will happen to Feng Suige,
if His Majesty dies?
He'll not only suffer the pain
of losing his father, right?
He'll also lose
everything he owns now,
including his life.
Are you threatening me?
You've taken it wrong.
In the past,
I cherished my friendship
with Feng Suige,
so I was reluctant to do anything
that could harm his life.
But if you ever blow my cover,
I'll have to
forsake my friendship with him.
In that case,
I'll have no reason
to hold myself back.
Feng Suige's life
is in the palm of your hand.
I can promise you
that whatever happens in the end,
I'll spare his life.
How about that?
You can make your choice now.
You know what?
I can kill you right now!
When whistling arrows are shot,
[Wutong Mansion]
the emperor will die,
and Susha will be in chaos.
Though you care about Feng Suige,
you must refrain acting on impulse.
[Log of City's Defenses]
Charge!
Take the shortcut!
Let's go!
Yes!
My Lord, run!
Go after them!
Go check it out.
Yes!
Your Highness!
Minister Hou is not here!
Your Highness,
they went that way.
Those people came prepared.
When the fight starts,
stay hidden somewhere.
If an enemy soldier escapes,
you must follow him
to their hideout.
Got it!
Minister Hou!
-My Lord!
My Lord!
Are you alright, My Lord?
The arrow was dipped in poison.
-Let's go.
-Move!
Who...
are you?
Kill them all!
Feng Suige,
though you're here today,
you can't save Hou Jing's life.
The Jinxiu death camp...
You must be Wu Ying.
I guess Yixiao keeps
no secret from you.
This is perfect.
Today,
it's time we ended all the feuds.
Your Highness must be joking.
How are there any feuds between us?
If I say there are, there must be.
Chief!
Your Highness,
I'll go after them with others.
Give it some time.
Your Highness!
Minister Hou was shot in the back.
Though it's not a vital spot,
I'm afraid there might be poison
on the arrow.
On our way back to the capital,
who knows what dangers are lying ahead.
Young Mistress Ling
should've arrived
at Zhengnian Villa by now.
Bring Minister Hou there
for treatment.
Got it.